Preliminary Inventory to the Carla A. Hills Papers, 1964-1993
Hoover Institution Archives
- Urban Homesteading Demonstration
  - Urban Homesteading Demonstration - Section 810
  - Urban Homesteading
- Urban Institute (Box 36)
- Urban Land Institute
- Urban Reinvestment Task Forces
- Urban Renewal Operations
- Urban Renewal Project - Park Central Towers - Cleveland, Ohio
- Urgent Needs Funds
- Vacancies in Multifamily Rental Units (Excluding Public Housing) Survey Report
- Vacancy Rates
- Vandalism
- Vanier Tower (R-79) Central City Redvelopment Agency Project, San Bernardino, California
- Valley Association of Cities
- Variable Interest Rates
  - Variable Interest Rates - Volume 3
  - Variable Interest Rates - Volume 2
  - Variable Interest Rates - Volume 1
- Ventura Townehouse Foreclosure
- Verterans Administration
- Violations of Administrative Control of Funds Regulations
- Volk, Robert - Shenandoah New Community
- Voluntary Contributions
- Wallace, Robert T., Deputy Under Secretary for Management
- Water Resources Council
- Wednesday Group Meetings
- Weicher, John C.
- Welfare Reform
- White House Conference on Handicapped Individuals
- White House Fellows
- White House Memoranda Volume 2, January thru June, 1976 (Box 37)
- White House Memoranda Volume 3, July 1976 thru December 1976
- White House Mess Regulations
- White House Public Forums on Domestic Policy - Impact on HUD
- White House Signal Corps
- White House Staff Meetings
- Wild and Scenic Rivers Act (P.L. 90-542), Amended by P. L. 93-621, January 3, 1975
- Williams, Senator Harrison and New Jersey Congressional Delegation, 2/24/76
- Wittenberg, Eric A.
- Wolf, Robert B.
- Women Presidential Appointees
- HUD Women's Caucus
- HUD Women's Programs
- Women's Educational Programs Advisory Council
- Young, James L.
- Zax, Leonard
- Accounting System for Billing/Collecting FHA Mortgage Insurance Premiums from Mortgagees, GAO Interim Report B-114860
- Action Being Taken to Correct Weaknesses in the System of Paying Taxes on Acquired Residential Properties, GAO Report, 11/26/75
- Administration of Federal Assistance Programs -- Case Study Demonstrating Need for Additional Improvements -- GAO Draft Report, 1/26/76
- Administration of Federal Assistance Programs -- A Case Study Showing Need for Additional Improvements -- Comptroller General REport B-164031 (5), 7/28/76
- An Overview of Federal INternal Audit, GAO Draft Report 7/1/76 - Final Published Report dated, 11/29/76
- Better Overall Planning Needed to Improve the Standard of Living of White Mountain Apaches of Arizona, GAO Report, 8/12/75
- Circumstances surrounding Approval of Mortgage Insurance for Cedars of Lebanon Hospital, GAO Report, 7/7/75
- Construction Problems with Country Club Estates, Merrinack, New Hampshire -- A Section 235 Project, GAO Report, 10/20/76
- Differences in Cost of Purchasing Houses in 7 States Through Departments HUD/Agriculture, GAO Report, 5/15/74
- Effective Follow-up System Needed to Implement Recommendations By Study Commissions in the Federal Government, GAO Draft Report, 7/31/75
- Efforts to Achieve Objectives of the National Flood Insurance Program, GAO Testimony, 11/12/75
- Efforts to Consolidate Housing Activities of HUD/Other Agencies, GAO Letter Report, 8/25/76
- Efforts to Achieve Objectives of the National Flood Insurance Program, GAO Testimony, 12/2/75
- Energy Conservation at Government Field Installations -- Progress and Problems, GAO Report B178205, 8/19/76
- Environmental Assessment Efforts for Proposed Projects Have Been Ineffective, Comptroller General Report B-170186, 7/22/75
- Evaluation and Analysis to Support Decisionmaking, GAO Exposure Draft, 12/9/75
- Examination of Financial Statement of National Flood Insurance Program, FY 74, Comptroller General Report, 9/17/75
- Examination of the Government National Mortgage Association Financial Statements FY 75, Comptroller General Report, 5/10/76
- Examination of Financial Statements Pertaining to Insurance Operations of FHA, FY 74, GAO Draft Report, 8/5/75
- Examination of Fiancial Statements Pertianing to Insurance Operations of FHA, FY 75, GAO Report, 11/11/76
- Federal Crime Insurance Program - How It Can Be Made More Effective, GAO Report, 4/11/75
- FDAA Activities RElated to Tropical Storm Agnes, GAO Letter Report, 12/31/75
- Federal Fire Safety Requirements do not Insure Life Safety in Nursing Homes Fires, Comptroller General Draft Report, 5/24/76
- Federal White Collar Classification should be better Controlled, GAO Draft Report, 6/30/75
- Financial Status of Major Civil Acquisitions/Military Construction Projects as of GAO 2nd Report., 6/30/75
- Formidable Administrative Problems Challenge Achieving National Flood Insurance Objectives, GAO Report, 4/22/76
- Further Action Needed to Make all Public Buildings Accessible to the Physically Handicapped, GAO Report, 7/15/75
- GAO Activity in HUD - Periodic Report (Box 38)
- Getting the New Communities Program Started: Progress/Problems, GAO Report, 11/15/74
- Government Can Save More U/Composite Check Program, GAO Report, 11/10/75
- GNMA Secondary Mortgage Market Activities, GAO Testimony, GAO Letter Report, 9/20/76; dated 11/29/76
- Greater Benefits can be Derived from Improved HUD Audits of Program Participants, Comptroller General Report B-114860, 11/25/74
- Hazardous Working Conditions in Seven Federal Agencies, GAO Report B-163375, dated 8/4/76
- Homes in Santa Fe, New Mexico, not Rehabilitated in Accordance w/ Federal Requirements, Comptroller General Draft Report, 6/24/76
- Impact of Acquired Single-family Properties on Urban Blight in Chicago, GAO Draft Report, 4/22/76
- Improved Government Assistance can Increase U.S. Share of Foreign Engineering/Construction Projects, GAO Report, 9/9/74
- Improvements Needed in Efforts to Achieve Objectives of the National Flood Insurance Program, GAO Draft Report, 12/17/75
- Improvements Needed in Efforts to Help the Mentally Disabled Return to/Remain in Communities, GAO Draft Report, 7/7/76
- Improvements Needed in Equal Employment Opportunity Program for Federal/Federally Assisted Construction Projects N.E., Oklahoma GAO Draft Report, 1/21/76
- Improvements Needed in Managing Automated Decisionmaking by Computer Throughout the Federal Government, GAO Report, 4/23/76
- Improvements Needed in Operation, Management/Administration of Leased Housing Programs, GAO Draft Report, 11/11/74
- Improving Federal Assistance to States for Radiation Emergency Response Planning, GAO Report, 11/5/75
- Integrated Grant Administration Program -- An Experiment in Joint Funding, GAO Report, 1/19/76
- Leased Housing Programs Need Improvement in Management/Operations, GAO Report, 7/11/75
- Little Progress Made in Insuring that Proper Rents are Charged U/ Section 236 Rental HAP, GAO Draft Report, 3/30/76
- Local Housing Authorities can Improve Operations/Reduce Dependence on Operating Subsidies, Comptroller General Report, 2/11/75
- Low Rent Public Housing Program at 2 Indian Housing Authorities/Our Los Angeles Area Office, GAO Report B-114868, 10/4/74
- Major Changes Needed to Make the New Leased-Housing Program Workable GAO Draft Report, dated 8/9/76
- Meeting Application/Review Requirements for Block Grants U/Title I of the Housing/Community Development Act of Comptroller General Report B-171630, 1974, 6/23/76
- National Rural Development Efforts and Impact of Federal Programs on 12-County Rural Area in South Dakota, Comptroller General Report B-114873, 1/8/75
- Need for Improvements in the Automated Payroll System of HUD, GAO Report, 6/18/75
- Need to Better Protect Home Buyers from Purchasing Defective Houses U/Federal Programs, GAO Draft Report, 1/27/76
- Need to Control Federal Warning System Proliferation, GAO Draft [UNK], 10/31/75
- Opportunity for Savings of Large Sums in Acquiring Computer Systems U/Federal Grant Programs, GAO Report, 7/24/75
- Opportunities to Improve Audit Operations, Comptroller General's Report to Congress, 10/19/76
- Opportunities for Savings in Interest Cost through Improved [UNK] Credit Methods in Federal Grant Programs, GAO Report, 4/29/75
- Part-time Employment in Federal Agencies, GAO Draft Report, 7/22/75
- Personnel Ceilings -- A Barrier to Effective Manpower Management? GAO Draft Report, 9/28/76
- Problems in Meeting Application/Review Requirements for Block Grant Funds U/Title I of the Housing/Community Development Act of GAO Draft Report, 1974 4/7/76
- Progress/Problems in Giving Rural Areas first Priority When Locating Federal Facilities, GAO Draft Report, 5/4/76
- Progress/Problems in Giving Rural Areas First Priority When Locating Federal Facilities, GAO Final Report, 9/7/76
- Proposed Rescission of HUD Budget Authority Relating to Section 236 Rental Housing Assistance Fund, GAO Letter Report, 7/7/76
- Protecting and Disposing of Single-family Properties Acquired by HUD GAO Report, 8/31/76
- Review of HUD's Management/Disposition of Acquired Multifamily Properties, GAO Letter Report, 10/29/75
- Review of HUD's Rehabilitation Loan Programs in Chicago/San [UNK] GAO Letter Report, 3/8/76
- Standard Budget Classifications -- Proposed Functions/Sub-Functions, GAO Report, 8/20/76
- Summaries of Conclusions/Recommendations on Operations of Civil Departments and Agencies, GAO Report, 1/9/76
- Sunbury Housing Project for the Elderly, GAO Letter Report, 10/3/75
- Tulsa, Oklahoma's Participation in the National Flood Insurance Program, GAO Report, 9/19/75
- Upward Mobility Programs in the Federal Government should be made more Effective, GAO Report, 4/29/75
- Using Independent Public Accountants to Audit Housing Authorities -- An Assessment, GAO Draft Report, 3/31/76
- Work Performed/Underway by GAO on Federal Regulatory Activities Comptroller General Report B-163628, 1/1/73 through 4/30/76, 7/20/76
- Advertising Council Inc. -, 4/1/76 (Box 39)
  - Correspondence - Speech Drafts/Final
  - Background
- Agronsky & Co -, 1/23/76
- Akron Public Affairs Forum
- Akron, Ohio -, 10/14/76
- American Assembly -, 10/28-31/76
- Arden House, New York
  - American Assembly
- American Association of Advertising
- Agencies (AAAA), The Greenbrier
- White Sulphur Springs -, 5/14/76
- American Association of Homes for the Aging (AAHA) -, 4/23/76
- American College of Trial Lawyers
- Dorado Beach, Puerto Rico -, 3/22/76
  - Background/Correspondence/Final
  - Drafts
- American Film Institute
- American Women in Radio and TV
- Washington, D. C. Chapter - EXHIBIT
- 75 Honorary Board Members
- Associated General Contractors of America (Speech information)
- Awards
  - Federal Woman's Award
  - Seventh Annual Awards Ceremony -, 12/7/76
- Budget of the United States Government - Fiscal Year 1977 (Box 40)
  - Presidential Budget Briefing
  - HUD Budget FY 77 Briefing Items
- Business Council -, 2/18/76
- Business Outlook Conferences
- Los Angeles, California -, 11/18/76
- California Delegation
- Meeting of 12/11/75 re Section 8 Problems
- California League of Cities
- San Diego, California -, 10/19/76
- California Trip -, 5/23-26/76
  - California Trip - Miscellaneous, 5/23-26/76
  - International Real Estate Federation Congress (FIABCI) San Francisco, California -, 5/24/76
  - Golden Circle Clubs - San Francisco, California - Los Angeles, California, 5/24/76
  - Hollywood Rotary Club/Chamber of Commerce Luncheon, 5/25/76
- Civil Service Commission Luncheon w/ Hampton and Jacobson -, 4/22/76
- City Club of Cleveland
- Cleveland, Ohio -, 10/8/76
- Commonwealth Club of San Francisco (Box 41)
- San Francisco, California -, 10/20/76
- Conable, Jr., Cong. Barber
- TV/Radio Taping -, 7/27/76
- The Conference Board Luncheon -, 11/16/76
- Current Biography
- Curzan, Myron
- Dallas Republican Men's Club
- Dallas, Texas -, 10/13/76
- Detroit Economic Club -, 11/1/76
- Detroit Press Club -, 4/14/76
- Speech Drafts
- Detroit Trip Briefing Book -, 4/14/76
- Economic Club of Indianapolis -, 9/22/76
- Edward (Jack), Lott (Trent) and Skies (Bob) -, 2/11/76
- Congressmen's T.V. Show
- Eldon Rudd Dinner -, 10/18/76
- Phoenix, Arizona
- Fair Housing Month Ceremony -, 4/2/76
- Federal Reserve Bank Board -, 10/6/76 (Box 42)
- Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
- Flint, Michigan Trip -, 5/13/76
- Florida Trip -, 10/28-29/76
- Orlando/Jacksonville
- Ford Foundation
- Ft. Worth Federal Business Association -, 9/28/76
- George Town Club
- Honorary Membership
- Habitat -, 1976
  - Post - Habitat Conference
  - Press - Miscellaneous
  - Memoranda
  - Declaration of Principles
  - Office Items
  - Forum
  - Schedule
  - Travel
- HABITAT (Box 43)
  - Habitat Advisory Committee Remarks -, 5/17/76
  - Habitat Delegation - Remarks -, 5/18/76
  - Speech -, 6/1/76
  - U. S. Delegation List
  - Russell W. Peterson - Remarks
  - Barbara Ward Speech (Lady Jackson)
  - News Releases
  - Press Clippings
  - News Summary (Bassett)
  - American Newspaper Coverage - Habitat - U. N. Conference
  - Miscellaneous Background Materials
- Harvard Business School Club of Washington -, 2/26/76
- Horizons on Display - Press Conference, 1/30/76
- Housing Conference for Women
- Illinois Press Association - Springfield, Illinois, 9/24/76
- Indiana Trip -, 4/30/76
- Indianapolis Economic Club -, 9/22/76 (Box 44)
- In the Bank... Or up the Chimney? A Dollars and Cents Guide to Energy Saving Home Improvements PD&R Study
- Junior League of Washington Christmas Shop
- Junior Woman's Club of Chevy Chase Maryland, Inc.
- Kettering Foundation, Charles F.
- Lake County Lincoln Day Dinner
- Painesville, Ohio -, 2/28/76
- Lakewood Republican Club
- Lakewood, Ohio -, 10/8/76
- League of Republican Women of the District of Columbia
- League of Women Voters
- Library of Congress
- Lincoln Day Dinner -, 2/10/76
- Lower Marion, Pennsylvania
- Los Angeles Advertising Women, Inc.
- McElyea, J. Richard -, 3/8/76
- Mortgage Bankers Association of America Breakfast Meeting with Executive Committee -, 4/13/76
- Mortgage Bankers of America
- San Francisco, California
- Panel Discussion -, 10/26/76
- National Association of Home Builders Convention -, 1/18-19/76
- Dallas, Texas
  - National Association of Real Estate Editors
  - Professional Builder of the Year
  - President's Video-typed Remarks
  - Background Materials/Speech Drafts
- National Association of Mutual Savings Banks (NAMSB) -, 2/25/76
- National Association of Realtors (Box 45)
- Houston, Texas -, 11/17/76
- National Consumer Information Center Convention -, 1/13/76
- Statler Hilton - Washington, D. C.
  - Correspondence/Final Speech
  - Drafts
- National Council of Negro Women
- National Governors' Conference
- Washington, D. C. -, 2/23/76
- Committee on Rural/Urban Development
- National Housing Conference
- Washington, D. C. -, 2/29/76
  - Speech
  - Questions
- National Urban League -, 8/2/76
- Boston, Massachusetts
- North Carolina Association of Realtors -, 10/1/76
- Ohio Municipal League -, 9/15/76 (Box 46)
- Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce
- San Jose, California -, 10/26/76
- Paterson, New Jersey -, 10/28/76
- Peoria, Illinois -, 3/12/76
- Section 8 Announcement/Rotary Luncheon
- Percy, Senator Charles -, 4/12/76
- Television Taping Interview
- Rangel, Charles B. -, 3/8/76
- Reader's Digest Interview -, 4/22/76
- Republican National Conference -, 2/6/76
- Scott, Senator Hugh -, 4/12/76
- Television Taping Interview
- Stanford University
- Commencement Address -, 6/13/76
  - Speech Drafts
- Supreme Court Historical Society
- TIME, Inc. -, 5/3/76
- Housing Industry Presidents
- Conference - Nassau
- U. S. Conference of Mayors
- Boston, Massachusetts -, 7/8/75
  - Official Program/Materials
- U.S. Conference of Mayors -, 6/30/76 (Box 47)
- Milwaukee, Wisconsin
  - Correspondence
  - Press
  - Schedule
  - Speech Outlines
  - Speech Drafts
  - Background
- U.S. Conference of Mayors -, 6/30/76
- Milwaukee, Wisconsin
  - Data Book
- U.S. League of Savings Association
- Miami Beach, Florida -, 11/11/75
  - Background/Correspondence/Final
  - Drafts
- Urban Institute Dinner -, 3/11/76
- Vice President's Public Hearings
  - Los Angeles, California -, 12/9/75
- Vice President's White House Public Forum (Box 48)
- Tampa, Florida -, 10/29/75
- Washington Association of Business
- Seattle, Washington -, 10/21/76
- Washington Press Club -, 9/12/75
- Washingtonian Magazine
- Charles Conconi Interviewer
- Briefing Paper for -, 12/19/75
- White House Briefing for Conference of Mayors -, 1/29/76
- White House Conference
- Omaha, Nebraska
- White House Consumer Conference
- Kansas City, Missouri -, 1/14/76
- White House Conference
- Seattle, Washington -, 9/4/75
  - Drafts and Final of Speech
- White House Meeting (Box 49)
- w/Synagogue Council of America
- White House Public Forums on Domestic Policy -, 1975
- Women in Communications, Inc.
- 33rd Annual Women of the Press Luncheon
- Los Angeles, California -, 5/23/75
- Women in Housing Conference
- Albuquerque, New Mexico -, 10/18/76
- Women's Week Ceremony
- Women's Week (HUD) -, 12/18/75
- YWCA - New York City -, 10/8/75
- Background/Correspondence/Speech
- "A" (Box 50)
  - American Bankers Association, 15th National Conference Denver, Colorado, 4/28/75
    - Correspondence/Speeches
    - Speech Drafts
  - American Bar Association - Montreal, Canada, 8/13/75
    - Correspondence/Miscellaneous
    - Final Drafts
  - American Bar Association Montreal Canada Briefing Books, 8/13/75
  - American Business Press White House, Rm. 450 EOB, 11/5/75
- "B"
  - Brooke/Pell T.V. Show, 7/23/75
  - Building Products Executives Conference, 10/23/75
    - Correspondence/Final Speech
    - Speech Drafts
- "C"
  - California Trip Briefing Book, 5/22 - 24/ 1975
- "F"
  - Face the Nation Appearance - 11:30 a.m. Washington, D.C., Sunday, June 29, 1975
  - Fair Housing and Equal Opportunity National Conference, 4/29 - 30, 1975
  - Fair Housing Month
  - Finch, Cliff (Governor Elect of Mississippi)
  - First Annual Housing Conference of the Federal Home Loan Bank of San Francisco -- Fairmont Hotel --, 12/10/75
- "H"
  - Housing And Development Reporter -- Advisory Board Meeting, 9/11/75
- "I"
  - Independent Agency Wives
  - International City Management Association Conference - Seattle, Washington, 9/29/75
    - Correspondence
    - Background and Speech Drafts
- "L" (Box 51)
  - Los Angeles Area Chamber of Commerce --, 4/4/75
  - Los Angeles County Bar Association, Los Angeles, CA. 5/22/75
- "M"
  - Mobile Home Manufacturers Association Reception Briefing Book, 3/18/75
  - Mortgage Bankers of America -- Meeting, July 22, 1975
  - Mortgage Bankers Association of America, Chicago, Illinois, 10/20/75
  - Correspondence/Misc./Final Speech
  - Speech Drafts
  - Mortgage Banker Interview --, 8/22/75
  - Munger, Tolles & Richershauser -- Reception, May 23, 1975
- "N"
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
    - Speech before NAACP Sheraton Park Hotel - 11:45 a.m. Washington, D.C., 7/2/75
    - Meeting with NAACP and Leadership Conference on Civil Rights (LCCR) Housing Task Force, 6/24/75
    - National Association of Home Builders
    - National Association of Home Builders, Washington, D.C. Board of Directors Meeting Speech, 5/19/75
    - National Association of HOme Builders, Washington, D.C. Dedication, National Housing Center, 5/17/75
  - National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials (NAHRO) Los Angeles, California, 10/13/75
    - Correspondence/Speech
    - Speech Drafts
  - National Association of Mutual Savings Bank - Washington Conference Breakfast, --, March 12, 1975 (Box 52)
  - National Association of Mutual Savings Bank
    - National Association of Mutual Savings Banks Boston, Massachusetts, May 12, 1975
  - National Association of Realtors Reception - Briefing Book, 3/17/75
  - National Association of Realtors San Francisco, California, 11/12/75
    - Background/Correspondence/Final
    - Drafts
  - National Cathedral School Assembly Address, 12/8/75
  - National Forest Products Association Annual Meeting L'Enfant Plaza Hotel, 5/6/75
  - Background and Speech Drafts
  - National League of Cities Miami Beach, Florida, 12/3/75
    - Correspondence/Final Speech
    - Drafts
  - National League of Cities Miami Beach, Florida, 12/3/75 (Box 53)
    - General Revenue Sharing
    - Background Materials
  - National League of Cities Miami Beach, Florida Briefing Books, 12/3/75
  - National Town Meeting, 9/10/75
  - New York Women's Bar Association President's Outstanding Woman Lawyer Award, New York City, 6/2/75
- P
  - People United to Save Humanity (PUSH) SPEECH Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 8/7/75
  - PUSH Speech, Philadelphia, PA., 8/7/75
  - Pepperdine University Commencement, Anaheim, California, 5/24/75
  - PERCY, Senator Charles H. Meeting of, 12/12/75
- "R"
  - REGULA, (Ralph)/O"Brien (George) Radio Interview Taping, 7/24/75
  - Republican Women's Forum, 11/21/75
  - RHODES, Congressman John Interview
  - ROBINSON, George ("Robbie")
- "S"
  - Savings Bonds Campaign, (1975)
  - Stanford March Band
- "T"
  - Tayloe House Reception (Housing Authorities)
  - Toote, Gloria E.A.
  - Turkish Aid Vote
- "W"
  - Washington Performing Arts Society Honorary Patrol
  - Winn, Congressman Larry, Jr. Television Interview, 12/5/75
  - Women's Lawyers' Association of Los Angeles, CA 9/21/75
  - Women's Expo `75 Department of Justice, 5/14/75
  - Women's Work
- "U"
  - United Mortgage Bankers of America, Inc. Meeting of, 7/28/75
- 1. Advertising Council, 4/1/76 (Box 54)
- 2. Akron Public Affairs Forum, 10/14/76
- 3. American Association of Advertising Agencies, 5/14/76
- 4. American Bankers Association, 4/28/75
- 5. American Bar Assocation, 8/13/75
- 6. American Business Press, 11/5/75
- 7. American College of Trail Lawyers, 3/22/76
- 8. HUD Awards Ceremony, 10/10/75
- 9. Budget Briefings, 1/20/76
- 10. Budget Briefing, 1/15/76
- 11. Building Products Executives Conference, 10/23/75
- 12. Business Council, 2/18/76
- 13. Business Outlook Conference in Los Angeles, 11/18/76
- 14. California League of Cities, 10/19/76
- 15. City Club of Cleveland, 10/8/76
- 16. Commonwealth Club of San Francisco, 10/20/76
- 17. Community Development Block Grant Report Press Conference, 1/8/76
- 18. Dallas Republican Men's Club, 10/13/76
- 19. Detroit Economic Club, 11/1/76
- 20. Detroit Press Club, 4/14/76
- 21. Economic Club of Indianapolis, 9/22/76
- 22. Eldon Rudd Dinner, 10/18/76
- 23. Fair Housing Conference, 4/29/75
- 24. Fair Housing Month Ceremony, 4/2/76
- 25. Fair Housing Month Signing, 4/8/75
- 26. Federal Reserve Bank Board, 10/6/76
- 27. Flint, Michigan, 5/13/76
- 27A Ft. Worth Federal Business Association, 9/28/76
- 28. Golden Circle Club, 5/24/76
- 29. Habitat Advisory Committee, 5/17/76
- 30. Habitat Delegation, 5/18/76
- 31. Habitat, 6/1/76
- 32. Harvard Business School Club of Washington, 2/26/76 (Box 55)
- 33. Hollywood Rotary Club, 5/25/76
- 34. Horizons on Display, 1/30/76
- 35. HUD Women's Week, 12/18/75
- 36. Illinois Press Association, 9/24/76
- 37. International City Management Association Conference, 9/29/75
- 38. International Real Estate Federation Congress, 5/24/76
- 39. Lincoln Day Dinner, 2/10/76
- 40. Lake County Lincoln Day Dinner, 2/28/76
- 41. Lakewood Republican Club, 10/8/76
- 42. Los Angeles County Bar Association, 5/22/75
- 43. Mortgage Bankers Association of America, 10/20/75
- 44. National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 7/2/75
- 45. National Association of Home Builders, 5/19/75
- 46. National Association of Home Builders (Dallas), 1/18/76
- 47. National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials, 10/13/75
- 48. National Association of Mutual Savings Banks, 5/12/75
- 49. National Association of Realtors, 11/17/76
- 50. National Association of Realtors, 11/12/75
- 51. National Association of Regional Councils, 5/28/75
- 52. National Cathedral School Assembly Address, 12/8/75
- 53. National Consumer Information Center Convention, 1/13/76
- 54. National Federation of Republican Women, 8/17/76
- 55. National Forest Products Association, 5/6/75